[{"answer": "I -- look, I am vice president of the United States of America.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "And you're comfortable with same-sex marriage now?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "I feel, Piers, that on the policy that the vice president was describing there, that they are in complete accord.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "I mean given the benefit of what -- of hindsight over the last 24 hours, do you still think that everything Joe Biden said is consistent with the president's position?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, again, I'm not going to make news for the president here.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "So why doesn't he just do it now?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I don't know the -- I know what you know about the details of this particular case.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "How big a danger does al Qaeda remain if we're still uncovering plots like this?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Well, the -- look, there's no question that we are coming back from the most -- the most vicious, the deepest recession since the Great Depression.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Is that the kind of theme that you'll be looking to press for the campaign?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, I made of it that Vice President Biden, you know, had a policy break from the president.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "What did you make of it?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Well, you know, people's beliefs are their beliefs, Piers.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Is it not better to be a bit more progressive, especially now your man has won the nomination, or effectively won it?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, the numbers I just cited, you know, are accurate.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "It's not sustainable to say you're worse off, is it?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the fact is, this is a lengthy process.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Which way are you guys heading?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Sounded like a lot of people I knew on the court.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Did you go along with that?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Yes, that's right.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Is he really?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I don't feel that much different in age from him.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "But she found that women and men are starting to lose their sex drives much earlier than they used to, and -- because of stress and toxicity and normal aging.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I could lie.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Did you ever see \"Threes Company\" or were you over in England?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "You know, such a long story.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "-- fascinated by somebody bursting with vitality like you and energy and positive thoughts could actually have a 30 years feud?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I was fired for asking to be paid commensurate with the men.", "docId": "120507pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What's the short version?", "qSentId": 435}]